I just want y'all to know that we are in a time loop and the biggest difference between this time
and the last time, which was the civil rights movement, is that there are no leaders because
there are not enough people lifting up leadership. Everyone thinks that they are just as smart as
everyone else, even if they haven't done the work, even if they haven't read the books,
it's really what it is. The American effort to brainwash people into thinking that everyone in
America is the best has been most effectively disseminated amongst black people who have
received the least of everything that America has to offer. And even we sit up here all day
misrepresenting how much we know. The arrogance is astounding and astonishing
to an intense degree that says, unless we get over ourselves, we're not going to get
anything. We're not going to get anywhere. I will probably delete this later. I'm ranting.